Hello, I'm Delight.
Today, I visited a famous bakery in Bojeong-dong Cafe Street in Yongin, Gyeonggi-do.
This bakery was previously introduced as a place that makes and sells cakes called Milk Block.
It is famous for selling various kinds of cakes as well as milk blocks.
Let's see the process of making various cakes together.
Prepare the eggs to make the cake sheet
Eggs are used a lot because you have to make a lot of them
mix with sugar
Do not knead the egg water immediately, but boil eggs in hot water
Put the beaten egg mixture into the kneader
butter
Mix butter with milk
Butter also boils
While the butter is simmering, prepare the soft flour
Sift the flour
Mix the flour with the egg batter.
Mix the melted butter with the dough in small amounts.
Put the butter mixed with the dough back into the kneader.
Pour the cake sheet dough into the bread tin.
Place the cake sheet dough in the oven and bake
Remove the baked cake sheet from the bread pan
Cool the cake sheet
While the cake sheet cools, prepare the fruit.
Orange
grapefruit
Cut the cooled cake sheets
Earl grey cake sheet
chocolate cake sheet
Drizzle syrup over the cake before adding the whipped cream.
Making whipped cream for the cake
Put the whipped cream into the mixing bowl
sugar
Baking liquor to get rid of bad smell
whip whipped cream
Place whipped cream on the cake sheet
Fill with fruits according to the type of cake
Put the cream on top of the fruit.
Repeat this process to create a layer of cake
Icing the outside of the cake
Icing is done in two parts.
Now it's time to do some serious cake decorating.
The decoration also varies depending on the type.
gold powder
Mix strawberry concentrate with whipped cream
Decorate the cake with strawberry cream
vanilla concentrate
Mango Concentrate
chocolate whipped cream
Chocolate whipped cream is used for chocolate cake
chocolate chips
sugar powder
Earl Grey cake uses both whipped cream and chocolate whipped cream
black tea leaves
custard cream
Fill the shoe with cream
Fill in the cream between the shoes as well.
chocolate syrup
macaron coque
green grape
Strawberry
Thank you for watching so far. See you next time with a delicious video :)